# **AMIT KUMAR**

# UI/UX DESIGNER

## SUMARY

Experienced UI/UX Designer with over 3 years in creating user-friendly and visually appealing interfaces for web and mobile apps. Skilled in wireframing, prototyping, and usability testing. Proficient with Figma. Strong collaborator focused on enhancing user experience and driving business success.

## EXPERIENCE

# Web Designer

Sep 2020 - March 2022

Flamingo Infotech

- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to identify and prioritize features and requirements
- Design the Website.
- Extramilevanlines
- Html | Css | Wordpress | Photoshop

## Web Designer

April 2022 - July 2022

IndoEuropean

- Create a Mailer for the client as well as Student.
- Collaboration with Digital Marketing Team
- Sending the mail to the Client/Vendor/ Student
- IndoEuropean
- Html | Css | MailChip | Photoshop

#### Web Designer

Sep 2022 - May 2023

Oss Education

- Developed and implemented highly scalable and optimize code for WEB / Mobile
- Responsible for all The Fronted.
- <u>LearnandLead</u> | <u>GlobalITSuccess</u>
- <u>Html | Css | JavaScript | Photoshop</u>

# **UI/UX Designer**

June 2023 - Working

CodeFire Technology

- Full Fill the Figma | Design requirement of the Client.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to gather requirements, analyze user needs, and define software specifications.
- Develope the Ui as per Client Requirments
- HTML | CSS / SCSS | Figma | React | JavaScript

# MAJOR PROJECT

- ExtraMilevanlies
- MoverJunction
- · Codefire.org
- <u>Danamojo</u>
- Koshika
- <u>Learn4Lead</u>
- DSucceed Learners

#### EDUCATION

**BCA** 

2015 - 2018

MDU

J.B.Knowledge Park

Intermediate (PCM) 2012 - 2014
Bihar School Examination Board, Patna
Singhia Collage Samastipur, Bihar

### SKILLS

HTML CSS/SCSS BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT/React WORDPRESS

PHOTOSHOP FIGMA Amp-HTML

GitHub